<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
  <gameList>
        <game>
          <path>./31in1realgame-multicart.nes</path>
          <name>31 IN 1 REAL GAME!</name>
          <desc>We would like to share with you all our own Multicart. 31 real games! Lots of laughs! Facepalms! Controllers flying accross the room! Mysterious secrets! Fake names! Repeat games with different sprites! Everything in 3 megabits full of love and kisses.</desc>
          <image>./31in1realgame-multicart.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20160101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <players>1</players>
          <genre>31 IN 1 REAL GAME!</genre>
      </game>    
        <game>
          <path>./assimilate.nes</path>
          <name>ASSIMILATE</name>
          <desc>In Assimilate you control an alien space ship named Ossan and your main task is to kidnap humans, while the forces of the earth try to stop you from that.</desc>
          <image>./assimilate.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120806T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nessylum Games</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>ASSIMILATE</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./blaster.nes</path>
          <name>BIG CITY SLIDING BLASTER</name>
          <desc>Sliding Blaster by NovaSquirrel, a homebrew NES game released in 2014.</desc>
          <image>./blaster.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20140602T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>HLC! Project</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>BIG CITY SLIDING BLASTER</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./bladebuster.nes</path>
          <name>BLADE BUSTER</name>
          <desc>Blade Buster is a SHMUP for the Nintendo Entertainment System. Gain as many points as possible in two minutes!</desc>
          <image>./bladebuster.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20100918T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>NovaSquirrel</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>BLADE BUSTER</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./bronyblaster.nes</path>
          <name>BRONY BLASTER</name>
          <desc>The story is that MLP got cancelled and bronies are going mad, rioting all over the world. They have taken over buildings and you have to free them. The game is going to be a platformer but for now it&apos;s more of a boss rush than anything else, but still gives you an idea of the game... Use A to jump, B to attack and arrow keys to move (Duh!) Start pauses the game (Re-Duh!). This game is not meant to be taken seriously, it&apos;s just a joke.</desc>
          <image>./bronyblaster.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20150226T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>FG Software</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>BRONY BLASTER</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>      
        <game>
          <path>./dabg.nes</path>
          <name>DOUBLE ACTION BLASTER GUYS</name>
          <desc>Action game.</desc>
          <image>./dabg.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20130101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>NovaSquirrel</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>DOUBLE ACTION BLASTER GUYS</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./driar.nes</path>
          <name>DRIAR</name>
          <desc>Take control of Driar and collect all the stars on each level to progress. You can walk around the screen (if you exit the screen on the right side you will reappear on the left side) - remember this and use this to your advantage. There are 38 levels in total.</desc>
          <image>./driar.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120226T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Adolfsson, Eriksson</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>DRIAR</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./fff.nes</path>
          <name>F-FF</name>
          <desc>A basic racing game. Hit select on the menu to get 2p split screen. Controls: D-Pad: Steer; B: Accelerate; A: Boost; Start: Start Game; Select: Enable second player (on menu) [v1]</desc>
          <image>./fff.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20180129T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Pubby</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>F-FF</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./flappybird.nes</path>
          <name>FLAPPY BIRD</name>
          <desc>Flappy Bird is a one button game where you need to get a bird trough pipes, while not colliding with it. As said there is only one button, so with this button you can give your bird some height, but the height is being reduced immediate again. So you need to keep clicking and keep the correct height, which isn&apos;t easy at all.</desc>
          <image>./flappybird.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20150226T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nioreh</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>FLAPPY BIRD</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./filthykitchen.nes</path>
          <name>FILTHY KITCHEN</name>
          <desc>The kitchen is filthy, clean it up!</desc>
          <image>./filthykitchen.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170203T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>dustmop</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>FILTHY KITCHEN</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./gravedigger.nes</path>
          <name>GRAVEDIGGER</name>
          <desc>Here is a homebrew release where you play as the devil avoiding bats and dig up headstones to restore the graveyard.</desc>
          <image>./gravedigger.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20071107T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Tarnow</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>GRAVEDIGGER</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./indivisibleonnes.nes</path>
          <name>INDIVISIBLE ON NES</name>
          <desc>Join Ajna as she battles through forgotten temples in search of her tapir, Roti! You can contact the developer on https://twitter.com/kasumidirect</desc>
          <image>./indivisibleonnes.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170901T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>KasumiDirect</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>INDIVISIBLE ON NES</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>       
        <game>
          <path>./invaders.nes</path>
          <name>INVADERS MUST DIE</name>
          <desc>Here is a NES Homebrew game with a similiar style as Space Invaders.</desc>
          <image>./invaders.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120304T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Sebastian Mihai</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>INVADERS MUST DIE</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>     
        <game>
          <path>./jetpaco.nes</path>
          <name>JET PACO - SPACE AGENT!</name>
          <desc>Taking control of Paco Rebollez, you&apos;re tasked with finding and gathering energonia crystals, a rare and unusual material used to energise spacecrafts. To help with his journey, Paco is equipped with a state of the art jet pack which allows our homebrew hero to glide around the many rooms of an abandonded ship containing gems galore.</desc>
          <image>./jetpaco.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20150106T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>JET PACO - SPACE AGENT!</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>      
        <game>
          <path>./lala.nes</path>
          <name>LALA THE MAGICAL</name>
          <desc>Help Lala get the Wand and travel to the Sky Palace to find the three Power Gems! Just because she&apos;s bored!</desc>
          <image>./lala.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20150106T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>LALA THE MAGICAL</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./lightshields.nes</path>
          <name>LIGHTSHIELDS</name>
          <desc>A space-themed 2-player shooter game. Each player controls one spaceship and one light shield. Use your shield to deflect your opponent's bullets back at them, but don't let your own shield get in the way of your killshot!</desc>
          <image>./lightshields.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20180201T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Zutano Games</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>LIGHTSHIELDS</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./lunarlimit.nes</path>
          <name>LUNAR LIMIT</name>
          <desc>An early 80s arcade shooter for the NES. Play it on an emulator or NES hardware! Lunar Limit puts you in control of a miniature version of planet earth, "Mini Earth", and your faithful satellite, "The Moon Cannon", in an all-out-war against evil Atari invaders.</desc>
          <image>./lunarlimit.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Pubby</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>LUNAR LIMIT</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./mashymashy.nes</path>
          <name>MASHYMASHY</name>
          <desc>This straddles the line between game and tool. It is for testing mash speed. You set a mash button (A, B, Start, Select or "B with down" to simulate Ninja Gaiden Jaquio mashing. You set a time limit (1, 2, 5 or 10 seconds). Once time is complete, it will display number of buttons mashed and the rate of button pushes per second.</desc>
          <image>./mashymashy.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170109T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Mitch3a</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>MASHYMASHY</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./mineshaft.nes</path>
          <name>MINESHAFT</name>
          <desc>In this homebrew release you must slowly descend down a mineshaft as if you rush to the bottom, you will die.</desc>
          <image>./mineshaft.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120204T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nioreh</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>MINESHAFT</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./mouser2.nes</path>
          <name>MOUSER II</name>
          <desc>You play as a mouse who must run around and collect the pieces of cheese. Be careful not to run into any objects!</desc>
          <image>./mouser2.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20120212T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Tony Young</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>MOUSER II</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./nomolos.nes</path>
          <name>NOMOLOS: STORMING THE CATSLE</name>
          <desc>Storming the Catsle, is back! Originally released in 2012, this well known NES homebrew takes its inspiration from the great side-scrolling classics of the 80s</desc>
          <image>./nomolos.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20141015T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Gradual Games</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>NOMOLOS: STORMING THE CATSLE</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./novathesquirrel.nes</path>
          <name>NOVA THE SQUIRREL</name>
          <desc>Nova the Squirrel is an NES game that stars Nova Storm, a green squirrel, who ends up in a strange world at a convenient time, and has to use her new abilities to save it. It's a platformer that mostly focuses on Kirby-style ability copying and puzzle mechanics.</desc>
          <image>./novathesquirrel.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20180710T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>NovaSquirrel</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>NOVA THE SQUIRREL</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./ralph4.nes</path>
          <name>RALPH 4</name>
          <desc>A top-down game where the player controls Ralph, a happy dwarf in a blue outfit, and must guide him through 20 floors of the Evil Bear Lair. Be careful to not run Ralph into the bears that roam the Lair, as doing so kills Ralph and he will have to restart the floor.</desc>
          <image>./ralph4.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20160418T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Pubby</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>RALPH 4</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./rhde.nes</path>
          <name>RHDE FURNITURE FIGHT</name>
          <desc>A neighborhood feud has escalated. Make your house look better by breaking into your opponent&apos;s house and stealing the furniture.</desc>
          <image>./rhde.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20140324T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Damian Yerrick</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>RHDE FURNITURE FIGHT</genre>
          <players>2</players>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./roboninjaclimb.nes</path>
          <name>ROBO-NINJA CLIMB</name>
          <desc>Robo-Ninja is at it again, this time practicing his climbing and jumping skills before setting out to save the world. In this NES game, you climb and dodge spikes, navigating 5 levels of obstacles.</desc>
          <image>./roboninjaclimb.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20171122T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nathan Tolbert</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>ROBO-NINJA CLIMB</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./roulette.nes</path>
          <name>RUSSIAN ROULETTE [Damian]</name>
          <desc>Here is a home-brew title which simulates a game of Russian Roulette. A zapper can also be used in playing this game. Released By: Damian Yerrick</desc>
          <image>./roulette.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20100704T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Damian Yerrick</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>RUSSIAN ROULETTE [Damian]</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>           
        <game>
          <path>./sgthelmet.nes</path>
          <name>SGT. HELMET - TRAINING DAY</name>
          <desc>Sgt. Helmet Training Day is an action platformer by the Mojon Twins, who released this nice game first on the ZX Spectrum. And now here it is - for the 8-Bit NES!</desc>
          <image>./sgthelmet.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20131209T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>SGT. HELMET - TRAINING DAY</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./sir-ababol-remastered.nes</path>
          <name>SIR ADABOL REMASTERED</name>
          <desc>Control Sir Ababol accross the Monegrian fields and gather 24 ababol flowers. To be able to progress in your journey you'll need some keys you will be able to use to open several doors to gain access to different sections. You can jump on the baddies to get rid of them, too. Be patient, think before you jump, and you'll be successful!</desc>
          <image>./sir-ababol-remastered.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20160201T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>SIR ADABOL REMASTERED</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./spaceymcracey.nes</path>
          <name>SPACEY MCRACEY</name>
          <desc>Spacey McRacey is a 4-player party style game in which you fly a spaceship, and get points for staying in the lead.  (If you are the only player, you will play against terrible bots) Different rounds will have different alternate objectives, such as the battle round, where you also get points for killing your enemies. Move your ship with the control pad.  Press A to shoot, although you can only shoot once every few seconds.  You can kill opponents by shooting them, or by colliding with them from above. The first player to 100 points wins the round. Win 3 rounds to win the game. From time to time, powerups will fly across the top of the screen. Shoot them to get that power for the rest of the round.</desc>
          <image>./spaceymcracey.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170407T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Nathan Tolbert</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>SPACEY MCRACEY</genre>
          <players>1-4</players>
       </game>
       <game>
          <path>./starevil.nes</path>
          <name>STAR EVIL</name>
          <desc>A simple remake of the A52 game. I tried to make it faster paced and less glitchy, while still keeping some the original charm. Controls: D-Pad: Move; A/B: Shoot; Start: Start Game [v2]</desc>
          <image>./starevil.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20180129T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Pubby</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>STAR EVIL</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./superpakpak.nes</path>
          <name>SUPER PAKPAK</name>
          <desc>SUPER PAKPAK is a 2-4 player Spacewar!|Thrust|Gravity force style game. At least two players are needed to start the game. HOLD button A at the start menu to begin a game. The game will begin after the counter counts to zero. In two player games, you need to get two kills in a round before the level ends. In three or four player games, the level ends when there is only one ship remaining. There are 12 scenes in the game, after the 12th scene the game is reverted back to the first scene. After any player gets 50 points, the game ends and the end screen will appear.</desc>
          <image>./superpakpak.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20100723T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>AOH Games</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>SUPER PAKPAK</genre>
          <players>2-4</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./owlia.nes</path>
          <name>THE LEGENDS OF OWLIA</name>
          <desc>Action-adventure game inspired by StarTropics, Crystalis, and the Legend of Zelda.</desc>
          <image>./owlia.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20160601T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Gradual Games</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>THE LEGENDS OF OWLIA</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
       <game>
          <path>./thewit.nes</path>
          <name>THE WIT.NES</name>
          <desc>A demake of Thekla Inc's 2016 game "The Witness" has you exploring a mysterious island* and solving puzzles. Developed over 2 months, this Nes ROM stands as a reinterpretation and tribute to the original work. Aimed at both players unfamiliar with the full game who want to learn what it's like, as well as veterans that need a fix of new puzzle panels to solve.</desc>
          <image>./thewit.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20160603T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>dustmop</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>THE WIT.NES</genre>
          <players>1</players>
       </game>
        <game>
          <path>./thwaite.nes</path>
          <name>THWAITE</name>
          <desc>A hippie guitarist who has visited your small town for years has gone rogue and launched ICBMs toward your town. Break out the fireworks that you had been saving for Independence Day, turn them into makeshift anti-ballistic missiles (ABMs), and shoot down the incoming missiles. Each of two silos starts with 15 ABMs. Place the aiming cursor in front of the incoming missile and fire an ABM to destroy it. Defend the town for seven nights (Sunday through Saturday) and you win! Screen shows cursor, missiles, balloon, MIRV, explosions, ammo, score, and time.Game play screen. Click to show or hide names of the game objects. You have to lead your shot a bit because it takes a split second for the ABM to arrive. But the explosion of an ABM is wide enough to destroy several missiles, so aim where the incoming missiles&apos; paths are about to cross. Balloons and multiple independent reentry vehicle (MIRV) missiles will release a payload of multiple missiles if not shot down promptly. At the end of each round, the silos are refilled with ABMs: 15 each or 20 if only one silo remains. A destroyed silo will get rebuilt at the end of a night or once you&apos;ve lasted one round with no destroyed houses. And if a house has been destroyed, one house will be rebuilt the next day. Later in the week, when more houses are gone, you need not worry about missiles aimed at wreckage. The game is over once both silos or all ten houses have been destroyed, or once you have survived all seven nights.</desc>
          <image>./thwaite.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20111208T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Damian Yerrick</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>THWAITE</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>       
        <game>
          <path>./tigerjenny.nes</path>
          <name>TIGER JENNY</name>
          <desc>Game is set in the same universe as &apos;Ittle Dew&apos; it takes place a thousand years before the events of that game. Battle your way through the forests to seek vengeance on the Turnip Witch who dwells in her castle.</desc>
          <image>./tigerjenny.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20140609T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Ludosity</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>TIGER JENNY</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./twindragons.nes</path>
          <name>TWIN DRAGONS</name>
          <desc>The infamous Cater Killar has kidnapped one of the twin dragons. Pick up your favorite character and go through a journey to help your twin, crushing the various dangers in different worlds.</desc>
          <image>./twindragons.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170217T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Antoine Gohin</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>TWIN DRAGONS</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>      
        <game>
          <path>./vigilanteninja.nes</path>
          <name>VIGILANTE NINJA</name>
          <desc>A new NES game (2015), action platform jumper. Jump, punch, throwing stars. 4 exciting levels and 4 bosses to fight. Dodge bullets, avoid spikes.</desc>
          <image>./vigilanteninja.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20150709T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Dougeff</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>VIGILANTE NINJA</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game> 
        <game>
          <path>./wo-xiang-niao-niao.nes</path>
          <name>WO XIANG NIAO NIAO</name>
          <desc>Lin Lin has to collect at least eight flies on her way to the toilet (which is located uhm... straight to the right) for the King to let her use it. The path is full of baddies which can hurt Lin Lin very badly, but luckily she can bounce on them with her butt. Lin Lin shouldn&apos;t let the screen go faster than her, she must RUN. And she still has to collect the flies. And pee. [v1.3e]</desc>
          <image>./wo-xiang-niao-niao.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20170407T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>WO XIANG NIAO NIAO</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
        <game>
          <path>./yun.nes</path>
          <name>YUN</name>
          <desc>The main goal is helping yun capturing every single being to fill the pantry of her restaurant. To capture her enemies, Yun must stun them by means of hitting them with a bubble. Once they are stunned, they can be captured just touching them. [v5]</desc>
          <image>./yun.png</image>
          <rating>0</rating>
          <releasedate>20180601T000000</releasedate>
          <developer>Mojon Twins</developer>
          <publisher>HOMEBREW ROM</publisher>
          <genre>YUN</genre>
          <players>1</players>
      </game>
  </gameList>